Oh-eh, ah-ah
Falling for the first time
I got feelings that I can't fight
Lord, please have mercy on me
Push play then I rewind
Thinking 'bout you every day and night
Boy, what you doing to me?
'Cause, oh
Something different 'bout the way you make me feel like
I don't know why can't control it
Takes hold of me, is this for real?
This must be love, baby
'Cause I've never felt quite this way
Think this is love, baby
Get weak when you callin' my name
This must be love, love, love
I think this is love, maybe?
'Cause I don't know what else to blame
Look, I've been going out of my mind
Got that goosebumps, butterflies
I don't even wanna play the game
'Cause you read me everytime
I've been guarded, but I think you picked the lock
Picking petals saying love me, love me not
Gotta keep my cool, what you make me do?
L-O-V-E got me fallin', I'm so into you
I've been really trying to be cautious with my heart
But I can't deny it, how you got me caught up
And the feelings don't lie
Something 'bout you really making me feel, feel, feel
This must be love, love, baby
'Cause I've never felt quite this way
Think this is love, baby
Get weak when you callin' my name
This must be love, love, love
I think this is love, maybe?
'Cause I don't know what else to blame
Why, oh, why?
Afraid to lose myself when I'm with you
There's nothing else I'd rather do
Why, oh, why?
Boy, you really made a mess of me
This that real love
This that real, it's that real
I give up
Just take my heart, ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh
This must be love, love, love
Think this is love (love), maybe? (Maybe)
'Cause I don't know what else to blame, no